(Leonard:)It actually looks good, Sheldon.
(Penny:)-Doesn't it?
-Yeah.
(Sheldon:)I suppose I could see myself
in a scientific boy band.
(Sheldon:)Of course, I'd be the dreamy one
and the smart one.
(Amy:)Sorry I'm late.
(Amy:)-What did you do?
-I gave him a new look.
(Penny:)-It's cute, huh?
-Yeah, it's cute. That's the problem.
(Amy:)I don't need other girls
to see him walking around
(Amy:)like sex on a stick.
(Sheldon:)She's right. I'm too hot.
(Bernadette:)I'm excited to meet Emily.
(Howard:)Me, too. I just hope
he doesn't blow it.
(Bernadette:)Why would you say that?
(Howard:)Because he's Raj.
That's his thing.
(Howard:)Beckham can bend it,
Ralph can wreck it, Raj can blow it.
(Howard:)Look, I don't want it to happen,
(Howard:)but odds are he's gonna
find a way to...
(Howard:)Oh, crap, I know that girl.